[Music]
lady recently crying in the middle of
the aisle at Target just in the middle
of ugly crying hard crying okay and I
was like oh no I should do something so
I'm in target I get myself ready she's
crying so hard I'd go right up to her
and I'm like excuse me ma'am I think you
mean to be in Walmart right now so
nailed that interaction yeah how about
how about don't cry and target Karen
okay I'm not paying an extra 15 cents
for macaroni and cheese to see you cry
target is for champions okay ridiculous
I don't have a cool middle name it's
Bernard it's let's did you say that
Bernard that's not cool right but it
sounds cooler when you say it all
together
Warren Bernard Hall the third right that
sounds more but no don't get excited I'm
the first don't get excited
when I was little I asked my mom I said
why why would you name me that maybe
seconds when you grow up if you come
into money I want you to have a name
that sounds like you deserve money right
which is cool but what does that say
about my sister Tanika
[Laughter]
that name clearly says you want fries
with that
[Applause]
spiders are more afraid of you than you
are of them false not real nope no
spider is more afraid of me than I am of
it okay no spider has ever caught me in
bed and been like well I am sleeping in
the living room tonight that's never
happened no no spiders ever seriously
considered burning its apartment down
cuz it found me you know that's never
happened no spiders ever been peeing in
the middle of the night and then I ran
past it and it peed all over itself okay
[Applause]
that joke is so much more real than I
want it to be it's she's a bad driver I
said it there it is
she's a bat she drives way too close to
other cars right but I'm a good husband
I don't mention it sometimes sometimes
it looks like she's gonna hit the car in
front of it sometimes I get scared it's
not cool sometimes I can i yelled things
out things like lord save you please
help me don't take me please don't take
me please it's a white minivan
please don't take so because of that now
she thinks I'm in the gospel music yeah
she thinks my favorite song is jesus
take the wheel see you're laughing I
didn't know that was a real song so two
days ago never just seen someone in
public is gonna talk to you and they're
just so white trash you don't have the
energy to deal with them so many crazy
people so this guy he comes up to me all
right
this is dude in Walmart covered in his
tattoos he comes up to me his opening
line to me the first thing he says he
goes hey man where'd you do your time
what I've done zero time everyone I've
never been to jail a day in my life
okay this guy's but he's like he's just
making an assumption about me he's
trying to connect with me and I was like
you know what I'm gonna connect with him
I'll meet him halfway
almost messaged him a little I was like
you know how it is man did five years in
Azkaban no big deal
yeah he he wanted to impress me so bad
he was like word all right cool cool all
that time in prison and you didn't read
one Harry Potter book seems seems kind
of like a waste you know I don't know
what he's up to now but I'm pretty sure
it's not reading so you guys you guys
have Waffle House here you have off the
old waffle houses have you ever Mineo
waffles have you never been a Waffle
House you guys my witnesses Waffle House
it's like a ma and pas style diner most
lower-end diner the food there is great
but it is a filthy establishment have
you been they you know the food is good
sometimes you got to bring your own
silverware right scary but I love to eat
there I have a friend she works at IHOP
as a waitress oh she feels snooty and
compared to this place so I was telling
me Warren please stop eating at the
Waffle House said why I love it and she
said cuz the girl who serves you your
breakfast there is probably the same
person who cleans the toilets there
there first I was like yeah look but I
remembered that's how it is at my house
[Music]